{"id": 1, "text": "Jai Janiany 8th Semester Undergraduate | Computer Science Engineering | UCE RTU, Kota +91 9772881151 | jaijanyani@gmail.com | 7/108, Malviya Nagar Jaipur (302017)  SUMMARY To seek an opportunity to apply my technology expertise along with my creative problem solving skills in an innovative software company.  EXPERIENCE   Machine Learning Engineering Intern , Forsk Technologies , Jaipur  (May,2017 – July,2017)     Learned the foundational concepts of data science and machine learning including python and statistics, enough time was spent on understanding the concept behind each algorithm and examples and case studies were done. Built some mid-scaled machine learning models using supervised and unsupervised learning.  Software Engineering Intern , Proxbotics Creations Technologies , Jaipur (May,2016 – July,2016) Developed and optimized various projects including ecommerce, booking & reservation, non-profit organization Websites, using technologies: HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, MySQL etc.                           Trainee at TecheduSoft , Kota  (May,2015) The course contains 15+ modules including Android Basics, fragments, screen designing, intents, various views, signing app, web servers, web services, notifications, etc.                                                        PROJECTS All projects are available on git: https://github.com/JAIJANYANI  Video Analysis for surveillance  -A command line app which takes all your CCTV feeds as input and filters feeds with abnormal events which results in 90% less videos to watch, Used image processing and deep learning algorithms, outputs all time-stamps of interesting events for all feeds.  Food Calorie Estimator -An android app to estimate calories present in food with still image. Trained own Data-set (Meal-net) using Transfer learning Built upon Inception V3, Proposed a Deep Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) with 48 Layers, Developed a REST API to integrate it in Mobile apps, Optimized total computation time ~ 2 Seconds.  CryptoCurrency Market Predictor - A Flask app to predict the future prices of various Crypto Currencies, implemented various supervised and deep learning algorithms such as LSTM (RNN), polynomial regression, using scikit-learn, tensorflow, keras etc.   Spam Filter -A REST API to Detect Incoming SMS or Email as Spam or Ham which can be trained on your own data set. Used NLP with Naive Bayes for Sentiment Analysis.  mailto:jaijanyani@gmail.com Image Classifier using CNN -An application which detects objects present in a still image, implemented convolutional neural network using open source machine learning library which can be run on multiple machines to reduce training workloads, classifies objects using pre-trained image-net model.  Online Student and Faculty Portal -A Web Portal to manage attendance of students and faculties, can be integrated to mobile apps. Uses Php, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, etc.  Tax Accounting -A Decentralized web app built on Ethereum Block-Chain using Truffle and Embark framework, which can be used to transfer funds between accounts which automatically deducts tax from the account.  TECHNICAL SKILLS Programming Languages  : C, C++ Web Technologies     : HTML, CSS Scripting Languages       : Python, PHP, BASH Database Management System  : MySQL, SQLite Operating Systems    : Microsoft Windows, Linux, UNIX Strongest Areas               :  Machine Learning, Data Science  COURSES  Applied Machine Learning , Applied Data Science , Exploratory Data Analysis & Data Visualization , Neural Networks & Deep Learning , Computer networks , Data Structures & Algorithms , Operating Systems , Cloud Computing , Data Mining , Block chain Essentials , Database Management Systems.  EDUCATION  University College of Engineering , Kota : Btech (Pursuing) in Computer Science Engineering  (2018)  St. Edmunds School , Jaipur : Senior Secondary (XII) Education Rajasthan  (2012)  St. Edmunds School , Jaipur : Secondary (X) Education Rajasthan  (2010)", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [41, 69, "DEGREE"], [72, 79, "ORG"], [81, 86, "GPE"], [86, 100, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [103, 123, "EMAIL"], [147, 154, "GPE"], [141, 147, "GPE"], [251, 266, "SKILL"], [324, 359, "DESIGNATION"], [362, 380, "ORG"], [383, 390, "GPE"], [392, 412, "DATE"], [455, 467, "SKILL"], [472, 488, "SKILL"], [499, 506, "SKILL"], [510, 520, "SKILL"], [658, 674, "SKILL"], [703, 724, "SKILL"], [728, 755, "DESIGNATION"], [758, 791, "ORG"], [794, 801, "GPE"], [802, 822, "DATE"], [875, 884, "SKILL"], [963, 967, "SKILL"], [969, 972, "SKILL"], [974, 977, "SKILL"], [979, 989, "SKILL"], [991, 997, "SKILL"], [1029, 1051, "DESIGNATION"], [1054, 1059, "GPE"], [1061, 1069, "DATE"], [1113, 1127, "SKILL"], [1341, 1370, "EMAIL"], [1372, 1387, "SKILL"], [1554, 1570, "SKILL"], [1575, 1588, "SKILL"], [1849, 1883, "SKILL"], [1885, 1888, "SKILL"], [1918, 1926, "SKILL"], [2043, 2049, "SKILL"], [2147, 2160, "SKILL"], [2180, 2185, "SKILL"], [2186, 2189, "SKILL"], [2221, 2233, "SKILL"], [2235, 2245, "SKILL"], [2247, 2253, "SKILL"], [2276, 2284, "SKILL"], [2380, 2384, "SKILL"], [2433, 2453, "EMAIL"], [2478, 2482, "SKILL"], [2605, 2621, "SKILL"], [2889, 2892, "SKILL"], [2894, 2899, "SKILL"], [2901, 2905, "SKILL"], [2907, 2910, "SKILL"], [2912, 2922, "SKILL"], [3007, 3015, "SKILL"], [3019, 3026, "SKILL"], [3183, 3184, "SKILL"], [3186, 3189, "SKILL"], [3213, 3217, "SKILL"], [3219, 3223, "SKILL"], [3251, 3257, "SKILL"], [3259, 3262, "SKILL"], [3264, 3269, "SKILL"], [3299, 3304, "SKILL"], [3306, 3313, "SKILL"], [3400, 3416, "SKILL"], [3418, 3430, "SKILL"], [3449, 3465, "SKILL"], [3476, 3488, "SKILL"], [3503, 3516, "SKILL"], [3519, 3537, "SKILL"], [3540, 3555, "SKILL"], [3558, 3571, "SKILL"], [3662, 3674, "SKILL"], [3744, 3777, "ORG"], [3780, 3785, "GPE"], [3807, 3835, "DEGREE"], [3846, 3864, "ORG"], [3867, 3873, "GPE"], [3876, 3892, "DEGREE"], [3921, 3925, "DATE"], [3995, 3999, "DATE"], [3929, 3947, "ORG"], [3950, 3957, "GPE"], [3959, 3969, "DEGREE"]]}
{"id": 3, "text": "Bernice TanSingaporeAssistant Compliance Manager at Aberdeen Asset ManagementExperienceAssistant Compliance Manager at Aberdeen Asset ManagementJanuary 2017  -  Present  (3 months)Senior Compliance Officer at Aberdeen Asset ManagementJanuary 2015  -  December 2016  (2 years)Compliance Officer at Aberdeen Asset ManagementJuly 2012  -  December 2014  (2 years 6 months)Intern at HSBC Global Asset ManagementJune 2011  -  September 2011  (4 months)EducationUniversity of London International ProgrammesBachelor’s Degree, Banking and Finance, 2009 - 2012Anglo-Chinese Junior College2007 - 2008Bernice TanSingaporeAssistant Compliance Manager at Aberdeen Asset ManagementProfile Notes and Activity (1)3/7/2017—View by Ayyaz Ahmad", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [11, 20, "GPE"], [20, 49, "DESIGNATION"], [52, 77, "ORG"], [119, 144, "ORG"], [87, 115, "DESIGNATION"], [180, 205, "DESIGNATION"], [209, 234, "ORG"], [234, 264, "DATE"], [275, 293, "DESIGNATION"], [297, 322, "ORG"], [322, 349, "DATE"], [369, 375, "DESIGNATION"], [379, 407, "ORG"], [407, 436, "DATE"], [456, 476, "ORG"], [520, 539, "DEGREE"], [541, 552, "DATE"], [580, 591, "DATE"], [591, 602, "PERSON"], [552, 580, "ORG"], [602, 611, "GPE"], [611, 639, "DESIGNATION"], [643, 668, "ORG"], [698, 706, "DATE"], [144, 168, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4, "text": "Personal particulars                          Name  : Khor Wei Xiang Joshua   E-mail : khorweixiang@gmail.com     Contact : +65 96738340                 Work experience   Aberdeen Asset Management Asia Ltd (SINGAPORE) AUG 2015 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 PRESENT   (Investor Services)        Working in a team on cash management for feeder fund administration covering Asia Pacific region.     Performing Transfer Agent oversight for Select range of Aberdeen funds.     Monitoring daily subscription and redemptions.     Understanding Distributor / Subscription Agreements.     Account opening (Obtaining ACRA, AML/KYC, CRS ASL documents etc).     Ensure timely dissemination of daily / monthly / quarterly reports to respective internal / external stakeholders.        Performing trailer commission for Select range of Aberdeen funds.     Ensuring calculation accuracy and timely payment of trailer fees to respective distributors.           CITCO FUND SERVICES (SINGAPORE) JUL 2013 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 AUG 2015    (Fund Accountant / Operations)        Preparing daily position, cash and OTC reconciliation for Everest Capital (US $2.2 billion AUM as of Dec 2014).    Production of daily deliverables in line with client service level agreements, managing to keep deviation below 5%.    Handling break resolutions with broker and client on a daily basis.     Producing Net Asset Valuation (NAV) daily estimates for Tiger Veda hedge fund.    Accounting for capital dealing (subscription and redemption) and fees (management and incentive fees).            PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS (SINGAPORE)  DEC 2011 - APR 2013    (Audit and Assurance Department)        Working in teams under tight datelines to complete statutory audits at client's office.     Understanding clients' business environment (Operations, competitors, performance etc).    Have done audit at Nike, Pacific Internet, Asus, DBS Bank, MFS Technology.    Assessing key risk areas and identifying effectiveness of internal controls. Examples-    Did purchase order (PO) have a purchase requisition (PR) being raised for approval.    Does purchase order (PO) match delivery order (DO) quantity and description.    Physical security of warehouse.     Ensuring cash balance supported by bank statements and reconciliation.    Communicating effectively within the team on planning and execution.    Building rapport and handling clients tactfully so as to manage expectations.       Education   The University of Sydney (AUSTRALIA)   Jul 2009 - Jul 2011  Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting major).       Computer skills    Microsoft office    Proficient in Word and Powerpoint.    Intermediate Excel skills (Short cut keys, pivot-table, v-lookup etc).", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[54, 75, "PERSON"], [87, 109, "EMAIL"], [124, 136, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [171, 205, "ORG"], [207, 216, "GPE"], [1090, 1106, "ORG"], [928, 947, "ORG"], [949, 958, "GPE"], [960, 968, "DATE"], [982, 990, "DATE"], [354, 366, "DATE"], [435, 443, "GPE"], [805, 813, "GPE"], [1133, 1141, "DATE"], [218, 227, "DATE"], [240, 247, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5, "text": "Lester Tan                                                   5 Leedon Heights Singapore 267939| (+65) 9385 9091 lestertanty@gmail.com|Linkedin| Available Immediately |   2 May 2017 To: Hiring Manager of Korea Exchange                                                                                                                                   Korea Exchange                                                                                                                                                            30 Cecil Street                                                                                                                                                       #24-03 Prudential Tower                                                                                                                            Singapore 049712 Re: Application for the position of Derivatives Sales Associate Please find this to be my candidacy proposal for the position of Derivatives Sales Associate with Korea Exchange in Singapore. I am Lester, a Singaporean who graduated from Durham University (UK) with a Masters with Merits (2:1) in Management (Finance) in 2016. Additionally, I also hold a Bachelors in Economics and a Diploma in Computer Engineering and had studied in Singapore, United States, Australia, United Kingdom and Germany. More importantly, I was a former Derivatives Trader with Boomer Capital. During this time, I traded a range of derivatives products, including FX, Fixed Income, Equity, Commodities in Japan, Australia, Singapore and USA. Prior to my postgraduate studies, I had approximately 5 years of Business Development experience with Aberdeen and Invesco Asset Management, where was with the Institutional Marketing team and my duties included developing new and existing B2B relationships with corporate clients, enhancing working relationships with local and foreign partners which included Banks, MNCs etc as well as marketing the firm’s investment capabilities, conducting training to Relationship Managers, preparing marketing materials to clients and taking part in developing distribution strategy within our coverage area in ASEAN including Singapore, Brunei and Malaysia. During this time, I was part of the team which managed to hit SGD 230million worth of sales in 2015. The products that I marketed included equities, fixed income, FX, distressed debt as well as several multi asset capabilities.   I pride myself as a sale driven, influential and entrepreneurial individual who seeks to pursue a successful career in Business Development. I am a native speaker of English, Mandarin, Cantonese and currently learning Korean.  Thank you and I look forward to hearing from you.  Best Regards, Lester Tan                                                                                                                                                                 (+65) 9385 9091 https://www.linkedin.com/pub/lester-tan/35/6a1/29                Lester Tan      5 Leedon Heights Singapore 267939| (+65) 9385 9091 lestertanty@gmail.com|Linkedin| Available upon 1 Month Notice |   Professional Summary  Graduated with a Masters with Merits (2:1) in Management (Finance) from Durham University. I am a Singapore Postgraduate with professional experience in Business Development, Client Servicing and Products Development. Seeking a Career in Business Development with Korea Exchange. A ERASMAS European Scholarship Recipient and CAIA 1 Holder, I was a former competitive athlete who is outgoing, confident with a determination to win in the corporate world. Academic Qualifications   Dissertation Overseas, Mannheim Business School (Germany) (June 2016 – Sep 2016)  MSc with Merits, Management (Finance), Durham University (United Kingdom) (Sep 2015 – Sep 2016)    BBA, Economics & Finance, RMIT University (Australia) (May 2008 - June 2011)  Diploma, Computer Engineering, Temasek Polytechnic (Singapore) (May 2003 – Apr 2006)  Academic Achievements   Recipient of the 2016 Durham Postgraduate Award  Recipient of European Union (EU) Erasmus Program Scholarship  Dissertation titled “Effects of the Sovereign Debt Crisis on economic growth and development in the Euro area and European Union countries” shortlisted for Durham Postgraduate Dissertation Awards Program 2017  Professional Qualifications   Chartered Alternative Investment Analyst (CAIA) Program, CAIA Association                         • Level 1 – Passed (September 2014)  Certification in Technical Analysis (CTA), Singapore Traders Society (STATS) (March 2011)  Certified in Capital Markets and Financial Advisory Services (CMFAs) Institute of Banking & Finance (IBF) Module 1b – Rules & Regulations for Dealing in Securities  Certified in Capital Markets and Financial Advisory Services (CMFAs) Institute of Banking & Finance (IBF) Module 3 – Fund Management  Certified in Capital Markets and Financial Advisory Services (CMFAs) Institute of Banking & Finance (IBF) Module 5 – Regulations for Financial Advisory Services              Certified in Capital Markets and Financial Advisory Services (CMFAs) Institute of Banking & Finance (IBF) Module 6A – Securities & Futures Product Knowledge              Certified in Capital Markets and Financial Advisory Services (CMFAs) Institute of Banking & Finance (IBF) Module 8A – Collective Investment Scheme II              https://www.linkedin.com/pub/lester-tan/35/6a1/29https://app.box.com/s/gyx9cynkdnx6fsmv78trciml4jhrn6ishttps://app.box.com/s/gyx9cynkdnx6fsmv78trciml4jhrn6is Professional Experience  Marketing & Client Service Executive, Aberdeen Asset Management (August 2013 – July 2015)    Developed and strengthened relationship with key institutional clients in the Distribution Channels and developing distribution strategy within coverage area   Developed and managed Portfolio of accounts consisting of Banks, Insurers and Independent Financial Advisors with an accumulated AUM of SGD230+mil  Conducted research on competitor's product offering and provided regular update to board of directors on fresh developments within the Asset Management industry   Conducted quarterly client due diligence review and screening as well as responsible for all on-boarding processes on behalf of the Distribution Team  Lead Manager on all Aberdeen Singapore’s preparation of regulatory reports  Proprietary Derivatives Trader (Equities Index), Boomer Capital (October 2012 – July 2013)    Top Junior Trader on the desk for 6 consecutive months  Successfully performing arbitraging and implementing trading strategies such as calendar and butterfly spreads across various derivatives products such as the Australian Bonds Yield Curve, Eurodollar, TED Spread and Nikkei 225 across all exchange  Part of the Team which generated a total net profit of USD1.2+ million during 2Q13  Developed a Trend-following algorithm programme using C# and overseeing the back testing phase along with 2 Interns  Client Service Associate (Institutional Marketing/Client Servicing), Invesco Asset Management (August 2011 – July 2012)    Tasked with growing the money market presence in the ASEANS region. Primary clientele included local companies and MNCs  Successfully clinched deals worth SGD40+mil in the first year   Managed key relationship with corporate clients and identify cross selling opportunities with new and existing clients  Assisted in client servicing of other portfolios including key institutional clients including Central Banks, Sovereign Funds and Investment Banks   Extraction and provision of daily, weekly and quarterly fund reporting to clients done within a strict timeline as well as authoring bi-weekly comprehensive research report on fund management industry trend   Memberships   Market Sector Leader of the Durham University Finance Society Fund Team  Active member of the Durham University Poker Society  Active member of the Van Mildert College Badminton Team  Active Member of the RMIT Finance Society  Active Member of the Market Technician Association (MTA)   Volunteer with Gentle Paws, a Non-Profit Dog Shelter, and ACRES   Language Proficiency  Fluent: English, Mandarin, Cantonese, and Hokkien  Currently Learning: Korean, Spanish", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [78, 87, "GPE"], [97, 111, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [112, 133, "EMAIL"], [170, 180, "DATE"], [185, 199, "DESIGNATION"], [203, 362, "ORG"], [831, 840, "GPE"], [884, 911, "DESIGNATION"], [977, 1004, "DESIGNATION"], [1009, 1024, "ORG"], [1028, 1037, "GPE"], [1044, 1050, "PERSON"], [1085, 1102, "ORG"], [1168, 1172, "DATE"], [1202, 1224, "DEGREE"], [1231, 1262, "DEGREE"], [1115, 1164, "DEGREE"], [1282, 1291, "GPE"], [1293, 1306, "GPE"], [1308, 1317, "GPE"], [1319, 1333, "GPE"], [1338, 1345, "GPE"], [1380, 1398, "DESIGNATION"], [1404, 1418, "ORG"], [1531, 1536, "GPE"], [1538, 1547, "GPE"], [1549, 1558, "GPE"], [1563, 1566, "GPE"], [1633, 1653, "DESIGNATION"], [1670, 1678, "GPE"], [1683, 1707, "ORG"], [2025, 2046, "DESIGNATION"], [2185, 2194, "GPE"], [2196, 2202, "GPE"], [2207, 2215, "GPE"], [2566, 2586, "DESIGNATION"], [1054, 1065, "NORP"], [2613, 2620, "LANGUAGE"], [2622, 2630, "LANGUAGE"], [2632, 2641, "LANGUAGE"], [2665, 2671, "LANGUAGE"], [2739, 2749, "PERSON"], [2916, 2925, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [2991, 3001, "PERSON"], [3024, 3033, "GPE"], [3048, 3057, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [3058, 3079, "EMAIL"], [3299, 3319, "DESIGNATION"], [3384, 3404, "DESIGNATION"], [3410, 3424, "ORG"], [3428, 3435, "ORG"], [3650, 3675, "ORG"], [3676, 3683, "GPE"], [3686, 3706, "DATE"], [3710, 3747, "DEGREE"], [3749, 3766, "ORG"], [3768, 3782, "GPE"], [3785, 3804, "DATE"], [3836, 3851, "ORG"], [3853, 3862, "GPE"], [3865, 3885, "DATE"], [3889, 3918, "DEGREE"], [3920, 3940, "ORG"], [3941, 3950, "GPE"], [3953, 3972, "DATE"], [4022, 4047, "CERTIFICATES"], [4083, 4111, "CERTIFICATES"], [4269, 4316, "CERTIFICATES"], [4317, 4321, "DATE"], [4354, 4394, "CERTIFICATES"], [4396, 4400, "CERTIFICATES"], [4411, 4427, "ORG"], [4472, 4486, "DATE"], [4490, 4525, "CERTIFICATES"], [4527, 4530, "CERTIFICATES"], [4533, 4558, "ORG"], [4560, 4565, "ORG"], [4568, 4578, "DATE"], [4595, 4642, "CERTIFICATES"], [4644, 4649, "CERTIFICATES"], [4651, 4681, "ORG"], [4683, 4686, "ORG"], [4761, 4809, "CERTIFICATES"], [4810, 4815, "CERTIFICATES"], [4817, 4847, "ORG"], [4849, 4852, "ORG"], [4883, 4943, "CERTIFICATES"], [4945, 4950, "CERTIFICATES"], [4952, 4982, "ORG"], [4984, 4987, "ORG"], [5071, 5118, "CERTIFICATES"], [5120, 5125, "CERTIFICATES"], [5127, 5157, "ORG"], [5159, 5162, "ORG"], [5242, 5289, "CERTIFICATES"], [5291, 5296, "CERTIFICATES"], [5298, 5329, "ORG"], [5330, 5333, "ORG"], [5550, 5611, "DESIGNATION"], [5613, 5638, "ORG"], [5640, 5663, "DATE"], [5920, 5938, "DESIGNATION"], [6315, 6333, "ORG"], [6295, 6307, "DESIGNATION"], [6371, 6401, "DESIGNATION"], [6420, 6434, "ORG"], [6436, 6460, "DATE"], [6470, 6483, "DESIGNATION"], [6974, 6998, "DESIGNATION"], [7043, 7067, "ORG"], [7069, 7092, "DATE"], [7151, 7157, "GPE"], [7780, 7800, "DESIGNATION"], [7808, 7825, "ORG"], [7875, 7892, "ORG"], [7930, 7950, "ORG"], [7988, 8008, "ORG"], [8032, 8061, "ORG"], [8063, 8066, "ORG"], [8086, 8097, "ORG"], [8167, 8174, "LANGUAGE"], [8176, 8184, "LANGUAGE"], [8186, 8195, "LANGUAGE"], [8230, 8236, "LANGUAGE"], [8238, 8245, "LANGUAGE"], [1104, 1106, "GPE"], [3217, 3235, "ORG"], [3192, 3212, "DEGREE"], [3124, 3182, "DEGREE"], [3244, 3254, "GPE"], [4699, 4745, "CERTIFICATES"], [6910, 6913, "SKILL"]]}
{"id": 6, "text": "Lim Zhi Juan    Blk 289D Bukit Batok St 25 #07-176 Singapore 653289  Mobile: +65 8388 1236  Email: zhijuan_lim@hotmail.com    CAREER OBJECTIVE    Motivated professional seeking to further career in Client Servicing; offering an in-depth knowledge of Portfolio Valuation and Middle Office Operations, and 4 \\xc2\\xbd years of working with and supporting client service functions in banking and asset management firms. Has transferable skills such as investigation of valuation discrepancies and responding to operations related queries on behalf of the Client Service team, coding and testing logic under Visual Basic for bespoke reports, and working knowledge of regulations such as the MAS Code of CIS.     KEY SKILLS    Charles River Order Management  Asset class knowledge (Equities, Fixed Income, Alternatives, Multi-asset)  Investigation of price gaps on Corporate Actions and Securities  Coding logic and knowledge on Database Management Systems (Excel, Visual Basic, Access)  Portfolio Valuation   Bloomberg   Lipper   MAS Code of CIS, CPF guidelines, RAP 7    PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE    Investment Operations Officer  Aberdeen Asset Management        June 2015 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Present  Prepare and review customised Valuation, Performance and Regulatory reports in accordance to clients\\xe2\\x80\\x99 IMA requirements.  Code macros that manipulate master data files and produce sector, country, and currency concentrations across funds for reporting.  Coordinate client lifecycle transition (CLT) events such as new wins, contributions and withdrawals, change of guidelines.   Investigate and report pricing errors under the guidelines set out in the Code of CIS for Aberdeen funds.  Review and ensure timely disclosure of expense ratio for Aberdeen funds calculated according to the regulations of the CPFIS.  Prepare Financial Statements for Aberdeen product funds in line with RAP 7 reporting framework.  Resolve operational related queries covering client reporting, Aberdeen in-house funds, client transitions, third party oversight.   Process order placements and reconciliation on Charles River.     Fund Accountant II   Bank of New York Mellon        May 2012 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 May 2015 (3 years)  Daily maintenance of funds comprising of various asset types; equity, fixed income, alternatives, multi-asset.  Review and approve exceptions on trades and corporate actions before releasing NAV.   Investigate and resolve stock and cash breaks with fund managers and custodians.   Perform daily price and corporate action check using Bloomberg.  Assist in project to enhance exception handling system for operational efficiency.  Enhance trade posting macro by building in checks on security country of risk.  Provide adequate guidance and write training manuals for new hires.     EDUCATION    CFA Institute          June 2013  Passed CFA Level 1     Nanyang Technological University, Nanyang Business School    August 2009- July 2012  Bachelor of Business (Hons) (Major in Banking and Finance, Minor in Entrepreneurship)     University College Dublin, Quinn School of Business      January 2011- May 2011  Exchange program (Ireland)    Ngee Ann Polytechnic, School of Business and Accountancy    April 2006- February 2009  Diploma in Banking and Financial Services", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [51, 61, "GPE"], [77, 90, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [99, 122, "EMAIL"]]}
{"id": 8, "text": "YOW TZE PING, MAGDALENE    Address  :  Blk 8A Upper Boon Keng Road #22-502  Singapore 381008  Contact  :  8188-8790  Email  :  Magyow@hotmail.com  Date of birth  :  19 April 1981  Availability  : Within 3 months                Academic Qualifications:      Qualified Chartered Accountant (Singapore) with the Institute of Singapore Chartered Accountants of Singapore (formerly known as Institute of Certified Public Accountants of Singapore)        Nanyang Technological University, Degree in Bachelor of Accountancy July 2000 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 July 2003        Anderson Junior College, GCE \\xe2\\x80\\x98A\\xe2\\x80\\x99 Levels Jan 1998 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Nov 1999        Convent of the Holy Infant Jesus (C.H.I.J. - Toa Payoh), GCE \\xe2\\x80\\x98O\\xe2\\x80\\x99 Levels Jan 1994 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Nov 1997       Working Experience:     Company : Aberdeen Asset Management Asia Limited   Overview : Global investment management group headquartered and listed in the UK with    global FUM of over GBP 300 billion.   Position : Finance Manager, Financial Reporting  Reporting to    : Head of Financial Reporting    Duration : June 2015 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Current    Responsibilities:    Assisting the Head of Finance in planning and managing the monthly / interim financial reporting processes which includes:     Co-ordinate and oversee the monthly reporting of all Asia Pacific entities to ensure accuracy and timeliness of reporting to Aberdeen parent company.   Ensuring compliance with internal and regulatory policies, procedures and internal controls.  Provide technical expertise and advise on adhoc basis for more complex accounting issues within Asia Pacific.    Assist in the supervision of 3 finance staff (Local team of 10 staff with 3 direct reports).    Leading a team of 3 individuals, my key responsibilities are:    Meet all regulatory and Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s reporting requirements and ensure timeliness and accuracy of monthly/interim accounts close Singapore, China and South Korea entities, which includes:    Financial reporting to Monetary Authority of Singapore (\\xe2\\x80\\x9cMAS\\xe2\\x80\\x9d) for Singapore Capital Markets Services Licence on quarterly and annual basis as required;    Working with Legal team to ensure timely filing of all statutory reports with the local regulatory authorities (e.g. ACRA and equivalent in other countries);     Liaising with overseas service providers for accounting/tax services on monthly accounts;    Ensure detailed and accurate schedules are maintained for audit & tax purposes;    Liaising with local and overseas auditors/tax agents on  any adhoc queries;     Preparation / review of local and overseas statutory financial statements;    Review corporate tax return workings with tax manager in preparation for interim / statutory reporting;  and    All other adhoc financial reporting (e.g. Singapore Statistics)  Work closely with Legal team and other relevant business units to review and contribute to the drafting of sound commercial agreements (e.g. Investment Management Agreements, Distribution Agreements, intercompany agreements etc.)   Perform monthly analysis on the business performance and suggest implications.    Achievements:    Completed the GST self-assisted compliance review within 2 months of join date.  Completed the setup of 2 overseas subsidiaries in Shanghai, China and South Korea within 3 months of incorporation.   Reviewed and streamlined the quarterly MAS regulatory reporting process by automating extraction of data.   Participated in the Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s initiative of an intra group service agreement and Asia transfer pricing policy agreements over spanning over 4 months.     Reason for leaving: Limited chances for growth and challenges.        Company : ARA Asset Management Limited, Singapore  Overview : Real estate fund manager in Asia managing total assets in excess of over S$26   billion including REITs, Private Real Estate Funds and Real Estate Management      Services; Listed on the Singapore  Exchange Securities Trading Limited (\\xe2\\x80\\x9cSGX\\xe2\\x80\\x9d)    Mainboard since 2007.     illion  tax return workings ; monthyl es.Position : Finance Manager, Corporate Finance  Reporting to    : Group Chief Financial Controller and Assistant Finance Director   Duration : October 2010 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 May 2015    Responsibilities:    Leading a team of 7 individuals, my key responsibilities are:    Manage and coordinate Corporate Finance Department operations, financial and budget management of the Group, which includes more than subsidiaries.   Establish financial and internal control policies and procedures, and ensure regulatory compliance to SGX rules, company and tax laws and conformance to accounting standards which includes SFRS/HK GAAP/Malaysia FRS/IFRS.   Responsible for group consolidation, analyzing and reporting monthly performance, annual budgets and forecasts of the Group.   Treasury and cash flow forecast, working capital monitoring and management of the Group in excess of S$80 million with relevant exposure to corporate capital fund raising programs (e.g. convertible bonds, medium-term- notes, credit facilities).   Manage the Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s held-for-trading financial assets, in excess of S$40 million; Monitor the equity market and report back to Group CFO with make appropriate proposals on investment / divestment decisions.   Preparation of results announcements for SGX reporting and any other routine announcements.   Preparation of ARA Group Financial Statements, Code of Corporate Governance Report and all related circulars in preparation for the Company\\xe2\\x80\\x99s Annual Report.   Meet all regulatory reporting requirements and ensure timeliness and accuracy of monthly/quarterly/annual closure for all local and overseas companies\\xe2\\x80\\x99, which includes:     Co-ordinating the annual and quarterly audit and tax activities process;     Liaising with both local and overseas auditors/tax agent on audit/tax queries;     Preparation and review of financial statements, segmental analysis and notes to the accounts in line with SFRS/HKFRS/IFRS;     Ensuring the timely filing of all statutory reports with the local regulatory authorities (e.g. ACRA);     Financial reporting to Monetary Authority of Singapore for Singapore REIT Managers; and     Financial reporting for the Hong Kong REIT Managers which are licensed under Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong.     Monthly review of the following as prepared by the team:     Review of payment vouchers, cheques and invoices as part of day-to-day operations;     Review of monthly employees business and travel claims to ensure in compliance with employee handbook administered by Human Resource Department;     All subsidiaries\\xe2\\x80\\x99 management accounts, which include fair value measurements and foreign currency cashflow hedging entries;     Inter-company reconciliations to ensure no out-of-balance and propose offsetting intercompany adjustments (where appropriate and efficient);     Monthly sub-group level consolidation and overall Group consolidation results;     Quarterly GST reports and submissions; and     Any other unusual fluctuations requiring further enquiry and review.   Maintain positive working relationships and negotiate overdraft and financing terms with bankers.   Liaise directly with corporate secretaries, bankers, lawyers and other professionals for ad-hoc projects as assigned by the Group CFO.     Achievements:      Successfully completed an S$100 million financing for the Group within 3 months.     Responsible for liaising with vendors for the review of the various accounting and consolidation software for implementation across all business units within 6 months of join date .    Hands-on, meticulous, diligent and ability to multi-task and prioritise in meeting 100% of the deadlines with a high level of accuracy.    Reason for leaving: Further career and development prospects.     Company : Xpress Holdings Limited, Singapore   Overview : Full range of print management services with a presence in Singapore, China,   Vietnam, Philippines, Hong Kong, Malaysia; Listed on the SGX Mainboard since 1999.   Position : Finance Manager  Reporting to    : Financial Controller   Duration : January 2010 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 October 2010    Responsibilities:    Leading a team of 6 individuals, my key responsibilities were:      Providing support to the Group Financial Controller and to the Senior Management in strategic business planning, management and controls.   Preparation of formal paper write ups for submission to the Board of Directors for approval according to the Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s corporate governance policies and investment risk management policies.   Provide financial support and advice to all business units and work directly with the business and operation department heads to resolve all operational issues that arise on a day-to-day basis.    Review, design, implement and streamline operational workflow and effective internal control systems for new retail operations and onsite print stations.    Treasury and cashflow planning and management.    Responsible for credit reviews and approvals for new and existing customers to manage and reduce the company\\xe2\\x80\\x99s credit risk exposure by 8%.    Ensure credit controls and policies are adhered to according to the Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s financial policies.    Participate in credit review and arrear management meetings and advise sales directors on credit controls strategy and legal alternative in handling default.    Ensure statutory, accounting standards and SGX compliance are adhered to at all times.    Review of weekly financial reports for projects with unusual gross profit margins and investigate reasons behind the deviation.    Responsible for all group taxation matters, including corporate tax, GST, withholding tax, and preparation of transfer pricing agreements to ensure compliance.    Liaise directly with external and internal auditors, corporate secretaries, bankers, lawyers and other professionals for ad-hoc projects as assigned by senior management.    Lead the finance department and be responsible for financial and management accounting, budgeting, variance analysis and statutory reporting on a timely and accurate basis.    Regular co-ordination and perform consolidation of the Group accounts for reporting to Senior Management and Directors and for quarterly announcements to SGX.    Assist the Group Financial Controller in quarterly announcements to SGX, preparing and submitting formal papers to the Board of Directors for their consideration and approvals.    Perform monthly reviews of financial performance of Print Stations within the Group which are located In Singapore, Hong Kong, Malaysia, Vietnam and Philippines.    Hands-on experience in completion full sets of accounts for investment holding entity which includes General Ledger, Accounts Payable, Accounts Receivables and GST submission.    Coordinated the work schedules of the department to suit finance operations for both Group and the Singapore Subsidiary.     Achievements:      Early confirmation after 3 months due to good work performance.   Implemented new credit controls and policies and ensured 90% compliance to the Group\\xe2\\x80\\x99s financial guidelines.   Co-designed and implemented new commission system with the Singapore subsidiary to automate the monthly computation of commission payouts, saving 7 man-days per month.   Was familiar with the accounting software system within one week of being introduced to it    Led an under-staffed department to meet 100% of financial reporting deadlines.     Reason for leaving: Further career and development prospects. Current environment has limited industry growth potential due to market saturation and intense competition from smaller and leaner companies.        Company : RSM Chio Lim LLP   Overview : One of the largest CPA firm aside from the Big 4 international auditing firms.   Position : Audit Manager   Reporting to    : Audit Director   Duration : October 2003 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 June 2009    Responsibilities:      Specialised in performing annual statutory audits for Small Medium Enterprises, Non-Profit-Organisation (\\xe2\\x80\\x9cNPO\\xe2\\x80\\x9d) and subsidiaries of overseas MNCs from USA, Switzerland, United Kingdom and Australia.     Experienced in performing audits for companies listed on the Singapore Stock Exchange (Mainboard)     Audit clients included industries from healthcare, shipping, manufacturing, fund management, construction, and wholesale and general distribution.     Very experienced in completing consolidations for clients with complex set-ups.     Ensure client is in compliance with the Singapore Financial Reporting Standards, International Financial Reporting Standards, Company\\xe2\\x80\\x99s Act, Income Tax Act and other relevant Singapore Statutes applicable to the organization.     Supervising an audit team of at least six in the professional, technical and personal aspects and provide extensive guidance to the team via On-the-Job-Training.    Regular review of accounts receivable and collection of outstanding balances from customers.     In charge of forecasting monthly budget and actual billings for on-going and completed projects.     Assist Partners and Managers in sourcing for technical accounting information to resolve identified and contentious issues.     Assisting audit clients in drafting and reviewing their financial statements.     Assist clients on completion of reporting packages especially for tight and urgent deadlines.    Regularly responding to audit clients\\xe2\\x80\\x99 queries on updates in the Singapore Financial Reporting Standards and the Company\\xe2\\x80\\x99s Act.     Multi \\xe2\\x80\\x93 tasking under pressure with tight and multiple deadlines especially during peak seasons.     Coordinating and prioritizing audit schedules with limited resources for client portfolio.     Appointed as Reporting Accountants for clients with intent to be publicly listed.       Achievements:      Coordinating and prioritizing audit schedules with limited resources for client portfolio.     Promoted to Audit Manager within five years of joining the firm.     Headed a team comprising of 6 members ranging from assistants to seniors.      Able to work in a stressful environment with immense pressures and under extremely tight deadlines often successfully completing audits within deadlines.     Exposed to a diversified range of industries, with portfolios including industries in healthcare, construction, shipping, manufacturing, trading and NPO\\xe2\\x80\\x99s.     Able to manage assigned audit clients and maintain good professional relations with them.     Successfully completed auditing and consolidating the firm\\xe2\\x80\\x99s second largest listed company within two months which included 25 local entities and 19 foreign entities.     Entrusted with one of the firm\\xe2\\x80\\x99s largest group consolidation which includes almost forty entities, within ten months of employment.     Twice involved in the public listing process on Catalist (previously SESDAQ) for one of our audit clients, who was successfully listed.    Always maintaining a hands \\xe2\\x80\\x93 on approach on all duties assigned, delegating within the team to ensure the end results are achieved.    Regarded as professional, mature, meticulous, diligent with a good head for numbers.      Reason for leaving: To seek a more meaningful career which I can become more passionate about      Familiar with the following Softwares:      Hyperion Financial Management    CODA Live    MRI (Accounting Software for real estate and property management)    Navision     Microsoft Dynamics AX     AccPac     MYOB     Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)    SPSS version 10.0 (Statistical Software)     Audit Command Language (ACL)     Integrated Accounting for Windows        For Testimonial References:  Available upon request", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 23, "PERSON"], [76, 85, "GPE"], [127, 145, "EMAIL"], [165, 178, "DATE"], [106, 115, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [257, 288, "DESIGNATION"], [289, 298, "GPE"], [309, 353, "ORG"], [386, 427, "ORG"], [517, 527, "DATE"], [557, 580, "ORG"], [619, 627, "DATE"], [657, 689, "ORG"], [773, 781, "DATE"], [822, 860, "ORG"], [1001, 1016, "DESIGNATION"], [1057, 1084, "DESIGNATION"], [1168, 1183, "DESIGNATION"], [1406, 1414, "GPE"], [1947, 1952, "GPE"], [2043, 2052, "GPE"], [431, 440, "GPE"], [449, 481, "ORG"], [540, 549, "DATE"], [641, 649, "DATE"], [751, 759, "DATE"], [941, 943, "GPE"], [1099, 1108, "DATE"], [1334, 1346, "GPE"], [1623, 1635, "GPE"], [1936, 1945, "GPE"], [1957, 1968, "GPE"], [2021, 2039, "ORG"], [2087, 2121, "ORG"], [2293, 2297, "ORG"], [2826, 2835, "GPE"], [3311, 3319, "GPE"], [3321, 3326, "GPE"], [3331, 3342, "GPE"], [3730, 3758, "ORG"], [3760, 3769, "GPE"], [3782, 3806, "DESIGNATION"], [3810, 3814, "GPE"], [3969, 3978, "GPE"], [3980, 4015, "ORG"], [4065, 4069, "DATE"], [4127, 4142, "DESIGNATION"], [4181, 4213, "DESIGNATION"], [4218, 4244, "DESIGNATION"], [4258, 4270, "DATE"], [4284, 4292, "DATE"], [4734, 4742, "GPE"], [6179, 6183, "ORG"], [6213, 6244, "ORG"], [6249, 6258, "GPE"], [6259, 6272, "DESIGNATION"], [6310, 6320, "GPE"], [6320, 6333, "DESIGNATION"], [6359, 6392, "ORG"], [6396, 6405, "GPE"], [7314, 7335, "DESIGNATION"], [7337, 7344, "DESIGNATION"], [7346, 7353, "DESIGNATION"], [7423, 7426, "DESIGNATION"], [7936, 7959, "ORG"], [7961, 7970, "GPE"], [8043, 8052, "GPE"], [8054, 8059, "GPE"], [8063, 8070, "GPE"], [8072, 8083, "GPE"], [8085, 8094, "GPE"], [8096, 8104, "GPE"], [8120, 8134, "ORG"], [8140, 8144, "DATE"], [8159, 8174, "DESIGNATION"], [8194, 8214, "DESIGNATION"], [8228, 8240, "DATE"], [8254, 8266, "DATE"], [8384, 8410, "DESIGNATION"], [10416, 10419, "ORG"], [10435, 10461, "DESIGNATION"], [10709, 10718, "GPE"], [10720, 10729, "GPE"], [10731, 10739, "GPE"], [10741, 10748, "GPE"], [10753, 10764, "GPE"], [11047, 11056, "GPE"], [11848, 11864, "ORG"], [11970, 11983, "DESIGNATION"], [12004, 12019, "DESIGNATION"], [12032, 12044, "DATE"], [12058, 12067, "DATE"], [12267, 12270, "GPE"], [12272, 12283, "GPE"], [12285, 12299, "GPE"], [12304, 12313, "GPE"], [12380, 12404, "ORG"], [12696, 12705, "GPE"], [12842, 12851, "GPE"], [13643, 13652, "GPE"], [14142, 14155, "DESIGNATION"], [15548, 15597, "SKILL"], [15722, 15739, "SKILL"], [15740, 15744, "SKILL"], [15769, 15786, "SKILL"], [15814, 15836, "SKILL"], [15847, 15868, "SKILL"], [15078, 15086, "ORG"], [15099, 15105, "ORG"], [15663, 15717, "SKILL"], [15746, 15751, "SKILL"], [15753, 15764, "SKILL"], [15838, 15841, "SKILL"]]}
{"id": 9, "text": "Microsoft Word - Husseyn Smili March 2017.docxHusseyn Smili Dubai, UAE +971561794222 | hsmili@gmail.com | Nationality: American  PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY   A versatile professional with an entrepreneurial mindset in and out of the corporate world. I have 10 years of relationship management and business development experience at top tier global banks focusing on acquiring and managing clients and assets across the MENA region. EDUCATION IE Business School MBA Master of Business Administration ▪ Creator of www.mimble.co  ▪ Co-founder of IE Fin-Tech Club  ▪ Coordinator of IE Basketball Team University of Toledo    B.B.A Bachelor of Business Administration Madrid, Spain January 2016 - December 2016    Ohio, United States of America August 2003 - December 2005 ▪ Received Dean’s List Honors for academic excellence, Spring 2004 and Spring 2005 ▪ Member of Alpha Kappa Psi – The Professional Business Fraternity American University of Beirut B.B.A Bachelor of Business Administration   Beirut, Lebanon September 2001 - July 2003 PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE ABN AMRO Bank N.V. Director, Relationship Manager    Dubai, United Arab Emirates November 2011 - January 2016 ▪ Focusing on new business development, increased growth of Middle East business by bringing in new assets from high/ultra high net-worth individuals, institutions and family offices in the MENA region ▪ Exceeded revenue targets each year by building on relationships with new and existing clients ▪ Conducted research and analysis across all major asset classes to advise and consult clients on bespoke investment strategies in both developed and emerging markets  Merrill Lynch Bank (Suisse) S.A. (Private Banking) Assistant Vice President Dubai, United Arab Emirates March 2007 - November 2011 ▪ Managed assets for high/ultra high net-worth individuals, family offices and institutions across the MENA region ▪ Received First Vice President award for exceeding annual revenue targets ▪ Consulted and collaborated across different teams and departments to optimize client investment portfolios and succession planning structures Ed-Smiles Import/Export Company Partner Shanghai, China July 2006 - February 2007 ▪ Built relationships with manufacturers and vendors of cement, wood and textiles in China, to market and sell to distributors in Bahrain, Saudi Arabia, Lebanon and Jordan Smiles Telecommunications Partner New Mexico, USA December 2005 - July 2006 ▪ Led and executed roll out of a new prepaid cellular phone company in New Mexico, partnering with over 30 retail outlets and the third largest wholesaler in New Mexico LANGUAGES   English (Native), Arabic (Native), Spanish (Conversational) OTHER INTERESTING INFORMATION   ▪ Created an online saving platform, www.mimble.co; IE venture lab selected finalist ▪ Co-Founded The Clean Team, a cleaning services company with 25 full time employees ▪ Co-Founded Mr. Shattaf, a travel accessory brand supplied to retail outlets in the UAE and Saudi Arabia ▪ Active volunteer in charities for refugees in Lebanon", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[17, 30, "PERSON"], [60, 65, "GPE"], [0, 14, "SKILL"], [31, 41, "DATE"], [46, 59, "PERSON"], [67, 70, "GPE"], [87, 103, "EMAIL"], [71, 84, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [119, 127, "NORP"], [291, 311, "DESIGNATION"], [263, 286, "DESIGNATION"], [413, 417, "GPE"], [436, 454, "ORG"], [455, 492, "DEGREE"], [537, 553, "ORG"], [591, 611, "ORG"], [621, 656, "DEGREE"], [657, 663, "GPE"], [665, 670, "GPE"], [671, 699, "DATE"], [703, 707, "GPE"], [709, 733, "GPE"], [734, 761, "DATE"], [773, 791, "CERTIFICATES"], [824, 828, "DATE"], [840, 844, "DATE"], [857, 872, "ORG"], [875, 911, "ORG"], [912, 941, "ORG"], [948, 983, "DEGREE"], [986, 992, "GPE"], [994, 1001, "GPE"], [1002, 1028, "DATE"], [1053, 1066, "ORG"], [1072, 1080, "DESIGNATION"], [1082, 1102, "DESIGNATION"], [1106, 1111, "GPE"], [1113, 1133, "GPE"], [1134, 1162, "DATE"], [1177, 1201, "DESIGNATION"], [1223, 1234, "GPE"], [1353, 1357, "DESIGNATION"], [1629, 1648, "ORG"], [1680, 1705, "DESIGNATION"], [1705, 1710, "GPE"], [1712, 1733, "GPE"], [1733, 1759, "DATE"], [1863, 1867, "GPE"], [2094, 2133, "ORG"], [2134, 2142, "GPE"], [2144, 2149, "GPE"], [2150, 2175, "DATE"], [2261, 2266, "GPE"], [2306, 2313, "GPE"], [2315, 2327, "GPE"], [2329, 2336, "GPE"], [2341, 2381, "ORG"], [2382, 2392, "GPE"], [2394, 2423, "DATE"], [2495, 2505, "GPE"], [2582, 2592, "GPE"], [2605, 2612, "LANGUAGE"], [2623, 2629, "LANGUAGE"], [2640, 2647, "LANGUAGE"], [2795, 2809, "ORG"], [2880, 2891, "ORG"], [2952, 2955, "GPE"], [2960, 2972, "GPE"], [3021, 3028, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 10, "text": "Microsoft Word - TYS_Resume_v2.docxTsoi  Yan  (Joyce)  Shum    15J, Evelyn Towers, 38 Cloud View Road, North Point, Hong Kong � jshum90@gmail.com � 6382-8036 HKICPA Student Member EDUCATION        Santa Clara University, California, United States                                                                               Jun 2012           Bachelor of Science in Commerce, Accounting           Major GPA: 3.60            Overall GPA: 3.43                                               De Anza College, California, United States                                                                                                                                              Business Administration                                     Overall GPA: 3.75                                              Dean’s List (2008 Fall, 2009 Winter, Summer, Fall, 2010 Winter)  EXPERIENCE      ABN AMRO Bank N.V., Hong Kong                                                      Jul 2015 – Present                                   Financial Cost Accountant  • Preparation of month-end closing for HK Branch, Shanghai & DJC UAE • Monthly, quarterly and annual preparation of schedules and deliverables for Head Office reporting • Preparation of data and analytics to support the filing of Basel III reports and Liquidity Coverage Ratio reporting  • Process invoices for Hong Kong Branch and ensure payments are made with appropriate authorization • Process staff reimbursement claims through Concur (Travel & Expense solution)  • Expense review for rebilling process to ensure accurate cost allocation to various business lines • Handle queries from business and other enabling teams across HK, UAE, Shanghai and Singapore in regards to cost actuals figures for the month • Provide variance analysis on profit and loss accounts and month end financial reports to management • Liaison with internal and external auditors, as well as tax representatives       Platinum Management Services Limited, Hong Kong                                                      Nov 2013 – Jun 2015                                    Assistant Accountant  • Oversaw full set of management accounts at a divisional and consolidated level, including preparation of month-end closing and year-end audit materials • Handled correspondence of fund transfer for settlement of securities trading and cash movement • Prepared weekly investment portfolio summary and stock position for HK & overseas stock market  • Liaised with external counterparts for securities lending and financing  • Responsible for cash management within operation team and bank reconciliation • Facilitated payments to vendor invoices, expense claims and intercompany transactions  • Performed monthly P&L variance analysis and provide qualitative commentary to senior management • Worked with management team in annual budgeting and forecasting to meet goals and objectives  • Project Coordinator of the implementation of new accounting system SAP        Citrus Lane, Inc., California, United States                                Apr 2012 – Sep 2013       Accounting/ Finance Consultant • Handled daily accounts payable processes, accurate processing of invoices, purchase orders, expense reports, credit memos, and payment transactions on Quickbooks • Updated cash dashboards and key operational metrics for board meetings to show favorable trends  • Performed monthly and year-end closing procedures including bank reconciliations to ensure accuracy • Renegotiated payment terms with vendors from Net 7 to Net 60 days to improve cash flow and facilitate company’s return to profitability  • Aggregated data and metrics to better allocate costs on shipping and fulfillment to increase margin by 40% • Oversaw chargeback activities, fraud analysis and response documentation • Worked closely with the management of six departments to track monthly departmental budgets and maintain accuracy against annual spending limits  ________________________________________________________________________________________________________ SKILLS                     Fluent in both spoken and written English and Chinese (Cantonese, Mandarin)                                   Proficient in Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint), QuickBooks, SunSystems, SAP, Smartstream", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 14, "SKILL"], [41, 59, "PERSON"], [116, 125, "GPE"], [129, 146, "EMAIL"], [199, 221, "ORG"], [223, 233, "GPE"], [235, 248, "GPE"], [327, 335, "DATE"], [346, 377, "DEGREE"], [379, 405, "DEGREE"], [411, 415, "GPA"], [440, 444, "GPA"], [491, 506, "ORG"], [508, 518, "GPE"], [520, 533, "GPE"], [748, 752, "GPA"], [675, 698, "DEGREE"], [879, 896, "ORG"], [1081, 1083, "GPE"], [1353, 1362, "GPE"], [1674, 1676, "GPE"], [1678, 1681, "GPE"], [2440, 2442, "GPE"], [2908, 2927, "DESIGNATION"], [3005, 3015, "GPE"], [3062, 3081, "DATE"], [4121, 4128, "LANGUAGE"], [4211, 4227, "SKILL"], [4229, 4233, "SKILL"], [4235, 4240, "SKILL"], [4250, 4260, "SKILL"], [4275, 4285, "SKILL"], [4287, 4290, "SKILL"], [4292, 4303, "SKILL"], [811, 815, "DATE"], [822, 826, "DATE"], [849, 853, "DATE"], [899, 908, "GPE"], [962, 970, "DATE"], [1015, 1040, "DESIGNATION"], [1092, 1100, "GPE"], [1107, 1110, "GPE"], [1475, 1481, "ORG"], [1683, 1691, "GPE"], [1696, 1705, "GPE"], [1894, 1902, "DESIGNATION"], [1915, 1934, "DESIGNATION"], [1941, 1977, "ORG"], [1979, 1988, "GPE"], [2042, 2061, "DATE"], [2097, 2117, "DESIGNATION"], [2975, 3003, "ORG"], [3017, 3030, "GPE"], [3088, 3118, "DESIGNATION"], [4133, 4140, "LANGUAGE"], [4142, 4151, "LANGUAGE"], [4153, 4161, "LANGUAGE"], [4242, 4248, "SKILL"], [4263, 4273, "SKILL"]]}
{"id": 11, "text": "Yee Choon Kit          547 Serangoon North Ave 3  #12-162  Singapore 550547 +65 9725 8036 choonkit.yee@gmail.com  EDUCATION  2006 - 2010  Singapore Management University (SMU)    Bachelor in Social Sciences (Honours)    Double Majors in Political Science & Finance     WORK EXPERIENCE  Sept 2015 – Current  ABN AMRO Clearing Bank N.V., Relationship Manager  Managing pool of hedge fund, proprietary trading clients trading multi asset classes   Contributed to 20% increase of revenue for my pool of clients in FY 2016  Onboarding clients through effective management and communication to internal stakeholders eg. Operations, Risk, Technical teams  Increasing ROE by efficient allocation of clients’ credit line  Strong understanding of Treasury and SBL services   In-depth knowledge of APAC equities & global futures/options markets  ETF creation/redemption expertise accumulated through working with fund managers  Opening up new markets and products offerings to clients  Adhering and performing due diligence checks and annual compliance reviews for clients  Strong negotiation skills for fees renewal and enforcement of tighter global regulatory requirements   Preparing client risk management and credit proposals   Appointed Co-Chairman for ABN AMRO Bank’s 2016 One Bank One Team initiative  Oct 2014 – Sept 2015 Mizuho Securities (S) Pte Ltd, Asst. Vice President, Futures Sales  Spearheaded Mizuho Securities’ Asia – ex Japan sales for futures & OTC swaps clearing and execution  Cross selling of financial products with corporate bankers from Mizuho Bank   Opened up new markets in South East Asia and Greater China  Established relationships with major energy/commodity traders (Sinopec, Unipec, Petronas, Vitol etc), financial institutions (Standard Chartered Bank, China Merchant Bank etc) & brokers  mailto:choonkit.yee@gmail.com Initiated the company’s first foray into the Taiwanese market by working with several top Taiwanese FCMs  Negotiated and brokered the company’s first Introducer Agreement with Neo & Partners, a local trading arcade  Implemented cost saving strategies and increasing sales figures by 25% to improve department P&L for FY 2014  Preparing credit reports and risk reviews for risk committee  Preparing KYC documents for new client onboarding  Part of the working group for company’s MAS audit in 2014  Jan 2011 – Oct 2014 Phillip Securities Pte Ltd, Senior Dealer   Headed the global and institutional sales at Contracts for Difference (CFD) Department  Started CFD prime service business and onboarded Baiduri Bank for white labeling business   Overseeing CFD business for Phillip Capital Australia and started an Asian CFD dealing desk to capture Asian AUM  Managing clients’ investment portfolio of US$10 million by providing investment strategies and trade execution services  Structuring new CFD equity markets for trading with counterparties Morgan Stanley & Deutsche Bank  Led a team of business analysts and crafted the ASX Equity & Index CFDs in 2013  Mentoring junior dealers with potential to head the CFD business in Australia and UK offices  Concluded the department’s first Introducer Broker Agreement with a Taiwanese investment fund  Presented at local and overseas investment seminars    PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS   MAS Licensed Trading Representative (Rep No: YCK300028559)  CMFAS M1, M2A, M5, M6, M6A & M8 certified   Professional Chinese in Finance & Accounting Certification from NTU  LANGUAGE & IT SKILLS   Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel & PowerPoint  Native speaker in English, Mandarin & fluent in Cantonese  Knowledge in FIX connectivity  Experience in using Trading Technologies, CQG trading platforms, Bloomberg EMSX", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [59, 68, "GPE"], [76, 89, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [89, 112, "EMAIL"], [125, 136, "DATE"], [138, 175, "ORG"], [179, 206, "DEGREE"], [220, 264, "DEGREE"], [286, 305, "DATE"], [307, 334, "ORG"], [514, 519, "DATE"], [793, 797, "GPE"], [1244, 1256, "DESIGNATION"], [1260, 1273, "ORG"], [1311, 1331, "DATE"], [1332, 1358, "ORG"], [1363, 1383, "DESIGNATION"], [1413, 1436, "ORG"], [1442, 1447, "GPE"], [1607, 1622, "GPE"], [1627, 1640, "GPE"], [1706, 1713, "ORG"], [1715, 1721, "ORG"], [1723, 1731, "ORG"], [1733, 1738, "ORG"], [1769, 1792, "ORG"], [1793, 1813, "ORG"], [1687, 1704, "DESIGNATION"], [1837, 1859, "EMAIL"], [2038, 2052, "ORG"], [2183, 2187, "DATE"], [2358, 2362, "DATE"], [2364, 2383, "DATE"], [2384, 2410, "ORG"], [2412, 2426, "DESIGNATION"], [2567, 2579, "ORG"], [2639, 2664, "ORG"], [2915, 2929, "ORG"], [2932, 2945, "ORG"], [3098, 3107, "GPE"], [3112, 3114, "GPE"], [3307, 3342, "CERTIFICATES"], [3368, 3399, "CERTIFICATES"], [3413, 3457, "CERTIFICATES"], [3477, 3480, "ORG"], [3520, 3534, "SKILL"], [3536, 3541, "SKILL"], [3544, 3554, "SKILL"], [3575, 3582, "LANGUAGE"], [3584, 3592, "LANGUAGE"], [3605, 3614, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"id": 12, "text": "Microsoft Word - CV - Renny Chong (M).docx\t\tSingapore Citizen  +65 9875 2288             renny.chong@gmail.com                                                        https://sg.linkedin.com/in/rennychong  \t\t\t \t  Cambridge Associates Asia, Singapore                 Manager, Investment Performance, Performance Reporting Group                Oct 2012 – Nov 2016 (4 years, 1 month)  Cambridge Associates is a pioneer in the global investment consulting space, overseeing an AUM of approximately US$142 billion and serving as a gatekeeper to institutional and HNW clients in Asia Pacific, Europe, North America, Africa and the Middle East with (SWFs, government-linked organisations, government/private pensions, universities, foundations, trusts and family offices). The group analyses, tracks and reports on clients’ portfolio performance.                  Abraaj Capital Asia Pte Ltd, Singapore                 Analyst, Fundraising (Investor Relations), Investor Engagement Group                           Nov 2016 – Jan 2017 (3 months)  The Abraaj Group is an institutional private equity platform with AUM of approximately US$10 billion across the emerging markets of Africa, Asia, Latin America, the Middle East and Turkey. The group is the client-facing arm that drives fundraising and provides client servicing to institutional investors. I. Investor Relations  § Fundraising –  o Created pitch book, due diligence materials and legal documents  o E.g. Due diligence questionnaire (DDQ), private placement memorandum (PPM), performance track record and competitor analysis slide decks to drive new fund raises  § Client servicing –  o Worked with investment deals team to provide quarterly updates on the funds’ portfolio companies and performance in Asia Pacific investor calls and meetings  o Optimised and maintained the CRM database and created comprehensive investor profiles for fundraising pitches RENNY\tCHONG\tProfile\tSummary\t\t § 4 years investment consulting (asset management) – client servicing/sales support, project and business management (front-to-back office) and investment performance   § Less than 1 year private equity – fundraising and client servicing (investor relations)  § 5 asset class product knowledge – equity, fixed income, hedge funds, private investments and real assets   § Experienced in managing institutional/HNWI client base across      5 regions – Asia Pacific, Europe, North America, Africa and the Middle East with global multi-cultural teams  § Bachelor of Science (Honours) – Statistics (National University of Singapore, 2008-2012; University of Alberta, Canada, 2010-2011)   § Completed CFA Level I   Experience\tI. Sales and client servicing  § Sales and sales support in client/prospect meetings –  o Subject matter expert on the firm’s product suite for clients and investment performance methodology/knowledge  o Contributions have led to increased new client onboarding year-on-year o Conducted investment performance training for global clients and internal stakeholders o Proactive in client servicing  § Creating client/prospect-ready meeting materials for internal and external use –  o Prepared slide decks and strategic plan for various initiatives for dissemination to clients and internal stakeholders  o E.g. RFP pricing for firm’s services, the rollout of a firmwide project for customised online portfolio monitoring and analysis, Optica Performance  Skills\t/\tHighlights\t§ Business Management: o Global project management (rollout new business line; profitability project increased profits 50%) o Business plan/strategy  o Utilising dashboards  o Competitor landscape analysis o Conducting presentations o Personnel management  § Sales/Client relationship management:  o Sales pitching leading to increased prospect conversions (30-50% increase in FY15/16) o Client servicing (follow up, requests, customising deliverables, product demo/training, presentation) o RFP requests o Client onboarding  § Portfolio construction/reporting: o Asset allocation (strategic/tactical) o Benchmarking o Investment performance calculation and attribution analysis \t\tSingapore Citizen  +65 9875 2288             renny.chong@gmail.com                                                        https://sg.linkedin.com/in/rennychong           \t\t\t\t\tII. Project management and business management  § Cross-department oversight and implementation of global initiatives –  o E.g. The roll-out of a new digital-focused business line in APAC o E.g. Profitability and cost reduction project has to-date led to at least a 50% increase in profits o Led and collaborated with other departments’ analysts and management on projects that would impact strategic business development items o Involved in planning, communications and roll-out of department and firmwide initiatives to stakeholders  § Change driver and implementation of new firmwide performance reporting methodology –  o Project driver and thought partner on firmwide review and implementation of new performance methodologies on long-only and private investments o Assessing impact of changes on client portfolios’ historical returns and a resource to consulting teams/clients on enquiries III. Additional value add  § Supporting clients’ portfolio growth leading to an increase in total client AUM by 13% over 12 months –  o Enhanced and ensured accurate investment performance to drive ongoing portfolio construction/rebalancing: asset allocation (strategic/tactical), benchmarking, investment performance attribution analysis  § Strong product knowledge in various asset classes – o Including equity, fixed income, hedge funds, private investments and real assets  Personal\tHighlights\t§ Overseas Community Involvement Project, Yangon – Myanmar (Team Leader) Planning and implementing the teaching curriculum for local children and village construction efforts § Interests  Reading, Investing/Business, Fitness, Trekking, Photography, Travel, History, Philosophy and Culture  § Customising and analysing of client’s portfolio performance to value-add to relationship –  o Included extra portfolio performance summaries to clients on top of standard deliverables o E.g. Highlighting performance drivers on a fund manager and composite level, performance attribution analysis o Customised deliverables for client-specific analysis and offered post-delivery client support", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[22, 33, "PERSON"], [44, 53, "GPE"], [63, 76, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [89, 110, "EMAIL"], [212, 237, "ORG"], [298, 325, "ORG"], [341, 360, "DATE"], [381, 401, "ORG"], [572, 584, "GPE"], [586, 592, "GPE"], [609, 615, "GPE"], [885, 918, "DESIGNATION"], [933, 951, "DESIGNATION"], [954, 979, "ORG"], [594, 607, "GPE"], [624, 635, "GPE"], [856, 884, "ORG"], [1006, 1014, "DATE"], [1017, 1025, "DATE"], [1038, 1054, "ORG"], [1170, 1176, "GPE"], [1178, 1182, "GPE"], [1183, 1197, "GPE"], [1203, 1214, "GPE"], [1219, 1225, "GPE"], [2390, 2402, "GPE"], [2404, 2410, "GPE"], [2412, 2425, "GPE"], [2427, 2433, "GPE"], [2442, 2453, "GPE"], [2490, 2509, "DEGREE"], [2534, 2566, "ORG"], [2568, 2577, "DATE"], [2579, 2600, "ORG"], [2602, 2608, "GPE"], [2610, 2619, "DATE"], [2635, 2661, "CERTIFICATES"], [4115, 4124, "GPE"], [4134, 4147, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [4160, 4181, "EMAIL"], [4473, 4477, "GPE"], [5735, 5742, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 18, "text": "Vince (King Sing) Leung  Tel: 9740-5018              vince.ksleung@gmail.com    Product Coverage  Cash Equity, Derivative, Index Futures, Commodity Futures, CB, OTC products, Repo trade    Work Experience  Acion Partners Limited             Apr 2017 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Current  HK based event-driven hedge fund  Operations Associate  Mange cash level among PBs to optimise usage   Generate daily risk &exposure report to front office  Handle daily middle office tasks  Liaise with IT & counterparties to enhance system operation  Compile monthly newsletter and attribution report  Monitor corporate action and reconcile with prime brokers & fund administrator        Nine masts Capital Limited             Aug 2015 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Mar 2017  HK based multi-strategy hedge fund  Operations Associate  Generate daily exposure report to front office  Reconcile position & cash on daily basis and resolve breaks if any  Monitor collateral movement and capital usage for portfolio managers  Book trades to both portfolio management system and fund administrator\\xe2\\x80\\x99s system   Resolve settlement issues and processing questions dealing directly with the portfolio managers, prime brokers, administrator, and trading counter-parties  Liaise with brokers on commission schedule update  Transfer positions between PBs to achieve better margining/ financing      Asiya Investments Hong Kong Limited            Feb 2013 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Jul 2015  Kuwait multi strategy Hedge fund focuses on APAC (Ex-Japan) region  Middle Office Analyst / Trader  Assist senior trader to execute order (cash equity and derivate)  Locate stock borrow loan and liaise with counterparties on re-rating periodically  Perform Pre-trade compliance check (cash and position)  Perform Pre-trade & Post-trade analysis  Maintain commission record and perform brokers\\xe2\\x80\\x99 review   Monitor corporate action events for the fund and submit election   Perform trade booking and resolve any settlement issue  Match trade details against counterparty record and resolve any discrepancy  Monitor margin / collateral level for the funds and arrange cash transfer across Prime Brokers if necessary  Perform position & cash reconciliation and resolve any breaks  Participate in operation due diligence enhance enhancement project in order to obtain audit standard \\xe2\\x80\\x93 ISAE3402      Prime Capital Management Limited           Mar 2010 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 May 2012  Chinese long/short stragey hedge fund focuses on Greater China region   Hedge Fund Operations Analyst     Liaise and co-check with custodian bank on investor unit of the funds     Perform KYC documentation checking for new client subscription  Instruct and monitor subscription and redemption order  Provide security PnL Analysis and attribution report  Compile daily and monthly NAV and reconcile against Fund Administrator\\xe2\\x80\\x99s record   Monitor margin and collateral movement and prepare for funding  Solve trade settlement related issue  Carry out trade booking and position/cash reconciliation on daily basis  Prepare weekly / monthly performance reports and newsletter and distribute to investors  Liaise with Prime Broker / Fund Administrator / Custodian on fund transfer and payment  Prepare stock loan report and reconcile against Prime Brokers\\xe2\\x80\\x99 record  Handle corporate action and book relevant information into system  Coordinate with IT department for in-house system implementation  Participate in setting up Multi-Prime Brokerages for funds which the progress required extensive communication and testing  Successfully develop in-house automated reconciliation using VBA   Streamline various reports to enhance operations efficiency       Quality Risk Management & Operations Limited             Nov 2007 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Feb 2010   Independent financial service company providing service in back / middle office and risk management for hedge funds in the Asia region  Operations Analyst  Provide PnL explanation on investment products  Generate various risk statistic reports (VaR Summary, Stress Test, Sensitivity Test)  Perform trade confirmation, trade booking, and trade reconciliation  Provide estimated NAV calculation and reconcile against Fund Administrators\\xe2\\x80\\x99 record   Handle queries from clients and provide assistant on daily basis  Compile weekly market commentary            HSBC       Nov 2006 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Feb 2007 & May 2007 \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Aug 2007  International bank group  Temporary Assistant \\xe2\\x80\\x93 Wealth Management (Investment)  Provide sale analysis on different investment products (Unit Trusts & Structure Products)  Gather information on subscription & redemption of investment products with HK region  Assist product managers in new product development  Monitor competitors\\xe2\\x80\\x99 activities thru internet and site visit  Coordinate with different fund houses for product supports      Education   HKU SPACE, Hong Kong (2012)   Postgraduate Diploma in Investment Management      Relative coursework: Analytical Tools for Investment Management, Equity and Alternative Investments, Portfolio Management      Simon Fraser University, Canada (2006)   Bachelor of Business Administration (Major in Finance)      Relative coursework: Investment Analysis, Derivatives Securities, International Financial Management, Corporate Finance and Fundamental Accounting      Language and Computer Literacy   Fluent in both verbal and written English and Chinese   Proficient in MS Office Tools (i.e. Excel- VBA, PowerPoint, Word, Outlook)   Proficient in Financial Systems (i.e. Bloomberg AIM , Bloomberg, Imagine Trading System, Eze Castle, Geneva)  Page 1 of 2", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [53, 76, "EMAIL"], [732, 734, "GPE"], [1386, 1406, "DATE"], [1420, 1428, "DATE"], [1498, 1528, "DESIGNATION"], [1530, 1550, "DESIGNATION"], [2344, 2377, "ORG"], [2419, 2426, "NORP"], [3142, 3154, "DESIGNATION"], [3156, 3175, "DESIGNATION"], [18, 23, "PERSON"], [30, 39, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [206, 228, "ORG"], [241, 249, "DATE"], [272, 274, "GPE"], [306, 327, "DESIGNATION"], [661, 688, "ORG"], [700, 708, "DATE"], [722, 730, "DATE"], [1351, 1386, "ORG"], [1474, 1478, "GPE"], [1483, 1488, "GPE"], [2467, 2481, "GPE"], [2488, 2520, "DESIGNATION"], [3178, 3187, "DESIGNATION"], [3266, 3279, "DESIGNATION"], [3690, 3734, "ORG"], [3747, 3755, "DATE"], [3768, 3777, "DATE"], [3916, 3934, "DESIGNATION"], [3903, 3907, "GPE"], [4346, 4350, "ORG"], [4357, 4365, "DATE"], [4379, 4398, "DATE"], [4412, 4420, "DATE"], [4448, 4467, "DESIGNATION"], [4889, 4901, "ORG"], [4903, 4912, "GPE"], [4914, 4918, "DATE"], [4935, 4967, "DEGREE"], [5100, 5123, "ORG"], [5125, 5131, "GPE"], [5133, 5137, "DATE"], [5141, 5195, "DEGREE"], [5420, 5427, "LANGUAGE"], [5432, 5439, "LANGUAGE"], [5456, 5471, "SKILL"], [5478, 5483, "SKILL"], [5485, 5488, "SKILL"], [5490, 5500, "SKILL"], [5502, 5506, "SKILL"], [5508, 5515, "SKILL"], [5557, 5570, "SKILL"], [5573, 5582, "SKILL"], [5584, 5606, "SKILL"], [5608, 5618, "SKILL"], [5620, 5626, "SKILL"]]}
{"id": 20, "text": "JAYDE YIP, CPA          yip.jayde@gmail.com  +852 5538-4284 / 1-347-688-9058 EDUCATION / CREDENTIALS         University of California, Berkeley                       May 2009                    Double Degrees:  B.A. Economics (Honours)    B.A. Statistics       CPA  – Active license. Passed all four exam sections with score of 90+ in a total of 5 weeks of preparation CFA  – Passed Level 1 & 2 on first try each with 2 weeks of preparation and scored >70% in 9 out of 10 sections (>51- 70% in 2)           – Level 3 Candidate June 2017  KEY QUALIFICATIONS   Resourceful finance professional with over 7 years of experience in the financial services industry   In depth knowledge in financial statements analysis, fund accounting, operation, fund set up and restructuring, investment product knowledge and valuations  Familiar with various valuation models such as DCF, OPM Black-Scholes, Enterprise Value, Market/Transaction Multiples and valuation metrics such as P/E, PEG, FCF, Debt/Equity, ERP, ROIC, ROE, EV/EBITDA, WACC, etc.   Experience with a variety of fund types including traditional long/short equity, fund-of funds, private equity, and both open and closed ended funds  Successful and rapid career progression due to outstanding performance, taken half the time to promote to Director level  Self-starter and team player who has a “Whatever it Takes” mindset, goal-oriented, highly curious, self-disciplined with a high level of integrity, and excels in a fast-paced, high pressure environment.  PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE Director of Finance, Acion Partners Limited, Hong Kong        Jun 16 – Present Oversees and manages the Finance and Operations function for the fund and the management company.  Responsible for the financial health of the company and fund, include monitoring working capital needs, cash flow forecasting, tracking assets and liabilities, prepare and reviewing financial statements, and performance analysis.   Sets up and negotiates investment advisor agreements, broker agreements, ISDA, CSA & other legal agreements with the support of internal/external counsel.   Partners with CIO and Business Development to attend investor meetings to promote the fund and attract capital inflow  Collaborates with internal and external teams (investment, business development, legal, fund administrators, external auditors, tax advisor, regulatory bodies such as SFC and SEC) to ensure the company and fund operate efficiently and meet all the financial reporting and regulatory requirements.   Prepares annual financial budget and cash flow projection.  Manages commission soft dollar allocation and usage, coordinate broker reviews and decides broker wallet allocation   Design, document and enhance financial control framework in line with industry best practice.  Maintains in house shadow accounting records and reviews weekly/monthly net asset value calculation from fund administrators; review portfolio valuations, ensuring fund’s valuation policies and procedures are consistently applied.  Review management fee and performance fee calculations, monitor capital flows and portfolio rebalancing.  Work with fund administrators, auditors and tax advisors in preparation and review of annual financial statements, tax returns for the fund and management company.   Work with the CEO / COO on ad hoc projects as required, such as presentation of financial information to boards, executive committees and investors.  Finance Manager (Acting Controller), Partner Fund Management, San Francisco, California     Jan 13 – Jul 15  Managed $5B AUM - 23 hedge funds across 5 strategies in master-feeders and standalone fund structures.  Served as a voting member on the valuation committee. Have experience with private company valuations, funds launching and restructuring.       Valuation projects  Reviewed valuation models, financial statements, board meeting materials and participated in calls with companies to analyze if current valuation is appropriate.  Models and metrics examined include – DCF, LBO, Comparables, EV, etc.   Reviewed capitalization tables and term sheets to determine valuation impacts from new financing rounds.  Leadership and Management  Served as the right hand of the CFO in management of all accounting and operational aspects of the funds.  Worked closely with management and liaised with trading, operations, risk, legal and investor relations teams on implementing firm initiatives and assisting CEO with leading the business strategically.  Took turns with CFO to represent the Finance team in investor due diligence meetings.  Actively managed and coached the Finance team which consists of five accountants.   Launched three sets of funds with new investing strategies and attracted roughly $50M capital working with PMs, marketing and capital introduction groups.    Set up and maintained relationships with brokers and vendors.  Participated in fee negotiations.  Acted as liaison with outside service providers (auditors – Ernst & Young, fund administrators – HedgeServ, brokers – Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, Credit Suisse, UBS, Bank of America, etc.), respond to their queries and resolve issues.  Projects: Streamline workflows and money saving – Turning visions into results  Collaborated with the five aforementioned prime brokers to create a universal process to improve cash management, successfully lower cash interest expense by > 25%.   Lowered fund tax bill by around 30% by building fund and investment level tax summary automation with results instantly available in query format, allowing the portfolio managers to trade with maximized tax efficiency.    Worked with IT team to build accounting and tax database in house and successfully automated many time consuming, manual tasks such as partnership income allocations. Actively managed the entire project from start to finish, including creating roadmap for programmers to follow, engaged in testings, and roll out of the final products to the firm.    Worked with head operations to create tax alerts in the trading program to avoid entering into trades that could put us in tax disadvantage.  Managerial review and sign off  Reviewed valuations of the entire portfolios consisting of equities, fixed incomes, derivatives and private investments.   Reviewed all portfolio reporting including annual audited financial statements, monthly NAVs, tax packages, investor statements and ad hoc reports.    Reviewed performance projection, month-end closing, expenses, capital flows, management and incentive fee calculations.  Evaluated the potential for tax and legal contingencies through analysis of proprietary documents.  Assisted risk manager and compliance officer to review investor risk and transparency reports, and regulatory reporting.   Oversaw and managed fund operations including OTC settlements, cash and collateral management, and break resolutions.   Fund Accountant, Partner Fund Management, San Francisco, California      Oct 11 – Jan 13 Won the Outstanding Operations Employee award. Promoted to manager in less than 1.5 years.       Accounting  Acted as team leader to oversee the financial statement preparation and annual audit process.   Reviewed monthly NAV packages, prepared monthly performance projection and accrual budgets to administrators.  Tax  Devised practical solutions to reduce fund tax liability through performing various analysis including wash sale, straddle, constructive sale, qualified covered calls, 988 & 1256 contracts, and QDI/short dividend testing.   Prepared monthly investor tax allocations, tax estimates, state/Fed K1s, partnership returns, and other misc. tax filings.  Operations  Responsible for pricing and settling OTC products including CDS, EQS, CFD, OTC options, rate swaps and bank debts trades. Recalculated and confirmed settlement cash flows with counterparties using Bloomberg/Markit valuation models. Provided instructions to prime brokers to release/accept wires. Oversaw cash, collateral and margin call management.  Worked closely with traders, administrators and counterparties to ensure accurate trading activities, positions and valuations are captured. Reviewed daily cash, MV, and position reconciliations and resolve any breaks/discrepancies.  Associate, Rothstein Kass (now KPMG), Walnut Creek, California                                             Nov 09 – Sept 11 Entrusted by managers to perform senior associate level of work starting in year 2. Made the senior associate promotion at the end of Sept 2011 prior to the resignation.   Audit  Performed audit on hedge funds with AUM ranges from less than $5M to over $5B.  Clients include onshore and offshore long/short standalone funds, side-by-side funds, master-feeder funds and fund of funds.  Applied various valuation methods to test the fair value of hard-to-value securities in clients’ portfolios.  Design and execute different fair value testing to the Level 1, 2, 3 securities designated under ASC 820 (formerly FAS 157).  Actively participated in all stages of the audit, including planning, fieldwork and completion.          Tax  Prepared and reviewed K-1s, tax estimates, and 1065 partnership income tax returns for various clients.  Performed tax testing for wash sales, straddles, short sales, constructive sales, short vs. the box strategies, unrelated business taxable income (UBTI) and section 1256 and 988 transactions.  Global Wealth Management Intern, Merrill Lynch, San Francisco, California                                             June 08 – Aug 08  Analyzed companies and mutual funds using various financial modeling and valuation techniques, such as Black-Scholes model and the discounted cash flow method.  Presented the findings to the financial advisors on a weekly basis.    Utilized Bloomberg terminal to perform research on the companies listed on the S&P 500 and other major indices.    1st place winner of a virtual portfolio competition among the interns.  Had a + 13% gain while S&P 500 was down -8%.  Participated in meetings with different fund managers to discuss potential business opportunities.   Assistant Accountant, UC Berkeley Accounting Department, Berkeley, California  September 06 – June 09  Prepared month-end closing, bank reconciliations, accounts payable, invoices and payroll calculation.  Audited petty cash envelopes and created databases to maintain records of invoices and creditor’s payments.  RELEVANT COURSEWORK        Financial Information Analysis    Mathematical Statistics & Data Analysis    Statistics Programming     Econometrics     Economic Demography        Macro/Micro Analysis        Financial Economics         Corporate Finance         International Business     Wage Theory      Labor Economics      Multivariable Calculus      Auditing      Tax Accounting     Advanced Financial Accounting       ACTIVITIES Member, American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA)                     November 10 – Present Member, Association of Women in Alternative Investing (AWAI)         September 10 – Present  HONORS AND AWARDS Outstanding Operations Employee; Omicron Delta Epsilon– Int’l Honor Society in Economics; President’s Education Award– Outstanding Academic Excellence; Who's Who Among Students in American Universities & Colleges  COMPUTER SKILLS Proficient in Bloomberg, Eze Castle Order Management System, Geneva Portfolio Management System, Thomson One Investment Management, CCH – Prosystem Fx Suite, GoSystem- Tax RS, Citrix, Unix, R, StarRez, Munis, Sungard Front Arena, BNA Research & Analysis, HTML, Adobe Pro, Microsoft Office  LANGUAGE - Fluent in English, Cantonese and Mandarin", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [24, 43, "EMAIL"], [45, 59, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [62, 76, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [109, 143, "ORG"], [166, 174, "DATE"], [211, 235, "DEGREE"], [239, 265, "DEGREE"], [369, 372, "CERTIFICATES"], [1539, 1559, "DESIGNATION"], [1561, 1583, "ORG"], [1585, 1594, "GPE"], [1602, 1619, "DATE"], [2397, 2400, "ORG"], [2405, 2408, "ORG"], [3327, 3330, "DESIGNATION"], [3333, 3336, "DESIGNATION"], [3463, 3479, "DESIGNATION"], [3480, 3497, "DESIGNATION"], [3499, 3523, "ORG"], [3525, 3550, "GPE"], [3555, 3570, "DATE"], [4243, 4246, "DESIGNATION"], [4476, 4479, "DESIGNATION"], [5072, 5086, "ORG"], [5087, 5102, "ORG"], [5103, 5116, "ORG"], [5118, 5121, "ORG"], [5123, 5138, "ORG"], [6935, 6950, "DESIGNATION"], [6952, 6976, "ORG"], [527, 537, "DATE"], [8295, 8304, "DESIGNATION"], [8306, 8331, "ORG"], [8347, 8357, "GPE"], [8402, 8418, "GPE"], [8553, 8562, "GPE"], [9571, 9588, "GPE"], [9453, 9484, "DESIGNATION"], [9486, 9499, "ORG"], [9501, 9526, "GPE"], [9832, 9841, "ORG"], [10159, 10179, "DESIGNATION"], [10914, 10964, "ORG"], [10993, 11014, "DATE"], [11023, 11075, "ORG"], [10906, 10912, "DESIGNATION"], [11370, 11379, "SKILL"], [11453, 11486, "SKILL"], [11487, 11512, "SKILL"], [11514, 11531, "SKILL"], [11558, 11563, "SKILL"], [11565, 11584, "SKILL"], [11586, 11598, "SKILL"], [11667, 11674, "LANGUAGE"], [10180, 10214, "ORG"], [10216, 10237, "GPE"], [10238, 10260, "DATE"], [11015, 11021, "DESIGNATION"], [11084, 11107, "DATE"], [11306, 11338, "ORG"], [11381, 11415, "SKILL"], [11417, 11451, "SKILL"], [11540, 11544, "SKILL"], [11532, 11538, "SKILL"], [11546, 11547, "SKILL"], [11549, 11556, "SKILL"], [11611, 11615, "SKILL"], [11617, 11627, "SKILL"], [11628, 11644, "SKILL"], [11676, 11685, "LANGUAGE"], [11690, 11698, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"id": 21, "text": "Aspen See Chun Chien  8 November 1989    Address:   700C Ang Mo Kio Avenue 6    #24-328 Singapore 563700  Mobile:  +65 8740 4432  E-Mail:  aspenccs@gmail.com  Nationality:  Malaysian (Singapore P.R.)      An acting Chartered Secretary with over 3 years of work experiences with the ability to work independently, and conversant with the Companies Act, Cap. 50 of Singapore as well as other relevant regulatory bodies.    EMPLOYMENT DETAILS  Accrafile Pte. Ltd.  Job Title: Chartered Secretary  21 January 2016 to current    To provide corporate consulting and advisory in regards to corporate law and governance to over 400 companies pursuant to the Companies Act, Cap. 50 of Singapore and other relevant regulatory bodies.   To draft relevant documents such as resolutions for board and shareholder meetings; minutes of meetings; and any other documents that are required on an ad-hoc basis.  Responsible for the development of the sales and marketing strategy within the company, as well to lead the secretarial department consisting of 10 members.  To develop and improve the standard operating procedures (SOP) in regards to corporate secretarial practice, as well to ensure that the integrity and accuracy of secretarial records for respective clients are being maintained.    TTC Wealth & Management Sdn. Bhd.  Job Title: Corporate Secretarial Assistant  15 September 2014 to 18 December 2015    To assist the Company Secretary in drafting the relevant documents such as resolutions for board and shareholder meetings; minutes of meetings; and any other documents that are required on an ad-hoc basis.  Responsible in ensuring that the secretarial file and records are properly maintained.    Corporate Alliance Pte. Ltd. (n.k.a. BDO Corporate Services Pte. Ltd.)  Job Title: Corporate Secretarial Associate  3 March 2014 to 31 July 2014    To provide corporate consulting and advisory in regards to corporate law and governance to a portfolio consisting of 80 companies pursuant to the Companies Act, Cap. 50 of Singapore and other relevant regulatory bodies, under the supervision of the Senior Manager.  To draft relevant documents such as resolutions for board and shareholder meetings; minutes of meetings; and any other documents that are required on an ad-hoc basis.  To liaise with corporate foreign directors in Employment Pass applications as well as the arrangement of documents.  Responsible in ensuring that the secretarial file and records are properly maintained.  ACHIEVEMENTS  Internal Control System  During my employment with Accrafile Pte. Ltd. and its Group of Companies, I was engaged as part of the development and programming team as I managed to implement a system that improves work efficiencies within the corporate secretarial department, together by formalizing a standard operating procedure (SOP). As a qualified individual and a Chartered Secretary, I had the necessary knowledge and experience to design a system that caters to the needs of respective team members. For instance, I have designed a database to upkeep accurate records of respective clients, as well to be able to generate relevant documents and agreements, which in turn neglecting any occurrence of possible human errors.  Master of Business Administration (MBA) Project  I am an author to a MBA project titled \\xe2\\x80\\x9cThe Importance of Corporate Governance in an International Context and Companies in Malaysia\\xe2\\x80\\x9d. During my time in Edinburgh Napier University in pursue of my MBA course, I have made emphasis onto corporate law and governance where I have performed an in-depth research in relation to my professional qualification, ICSA. By doing this study, I have also conducted survey with top management levels and professors, for ways to improve best practices and proper internal control system within an organization. As a result, accounting loophole and fraud may be avoided, which in turn improves the economy by attracting new foreign investment due to transparency, and accountability.  ACADEMIC BACKGROUND  Master of Business Administration (MBA)  Year completed: October 2013  Institution: Edinburgh Napier University, Scotland, United Kingdom  Major: General MBA  Author of Dissertation: \\xe2\\x80\\x9cThe Importance of Corporate Governance in an International Context and Companies in Malaysia\\xe2\\x80\\x9d    ICSA Qualified Individual (ACIS)  Year completed: March 2013  Institution: The Institute of Chartered Secretaries and Administrators (ICSA)  Major: Corporate Law & Governance  Elected as Associate (ACIS) in Singapore: 15 July 2016  Elected as Graduateship (Grad ICSA): 4 March 2013  ACIS Membership No.: 7066209    Advanced Diploma in Commerce (Business Management)  Year completed: February 2012  Institution: Tunku Abdul Rahman College (TARC), Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  Major: Corporate Law & Business Management  Graduation Award: Merit    Diploma in Business Studies (Business Administration)  Year completed: May 2010  Institution: Tunku Abdul Rahman College (TARC), Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  Major: Business Studies & Administration  Graduation Award: Merit    LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES  Tunku Abdul Rahman College (TARC), Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  Duration (Year):  2010 - 2012  Business Management Society (BMS)  Position Held: Public Relations Director  Activities: To organize and conduct activities relating to the role of a Chartered Secretary, particularly attending Annual General Meetings (AGMs) of public companies listed in the Exchange.    LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY  English:  Malay:  Mandarin:  Cantonese:   Native Language  Intermediate  Basic (Speaking, Listening)  Basic (Speaking, Listening)", "meta": {}, "annotation_approver": null, "labels": [[0, 20, "PERSON"], [22, 37, "DATE"], [88, 97, "GPE"], [113, 128, "PHONE_NUMBER"], [139, 157, "EMAIL"], [173, 182, "NORP"], [215, 234, "DESIGNATION"], [363, 372, "GPE"], [441, 459, "ORG"], [473, 492, "DESIGNATION"], [494, 520, "DATE"], [676, 685, "GPE"], [1328, 1359, "DESIGNATION"], [1359, 1398, "DATE"], [1416, 1433, "DESIGNATION"], [1699, 1727, "ORG"], [1736, 1767, "ORG"], [1782, 1804, "DESIGNATION"], [1815, 1843, "DATE"], [2019, 2028, "GPE"], [2551, 2569, "ORG"], [3229, 3268, "DEGREE"], [3413, 3421, "GPE"], [3453, 3480, "ORG"], [3654, 3658, "CERTIFICATES"], [4041, 4074, "DEGREE"], [4098, 4110, "DATE"], [4124, 4152, "ORG"], [4154, 4162, "GPE"], [4164, 4178, "GPE"], [4394, 4404, "DATE"], [4492, 4547, "DEGREE"], [4551, 4560, "GPE"], [4562, 4574, "DATE"], [4613, 4625, "DATE"], [4659, 4709, "CERTIFICATES"], [4727, 4740, "DATE"], [4755, 4788, "ORG"], [4790, 4812, "GPE"], [4821, 4856, "DEGREE"], [4876, 4938, "CERTIFICATES"], [4956, 4964, "DATE"], [4979, 5012, "ORG"], [5014, 5036, "GPE"], [5045, 5078, "DEGREE"], [5131, 5165, "ORG"], [5180, 5188, "GPE"], [5166, 5178, "GPE"], [5208, 5219, "DATE"], [5221, 5254, "ORG"], [5271, 5296, "DESIGNATION"], [5371, 5390, "DESIGNATION"], [5515, 5522, "LANGUAGE"], [5525, 5530, "LANGUAGE"], [5533, 5541, "LANGUAGE"], [5544, 5553, "LANGUAGE"]]}
